Finding Aid for the Lewis MacAdams papers LSC.2289
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Memorabilia
  - Family recordings (Box 131)
    - Rhea MacAdams, 1978 June 4; yrlsc_2289_131_001_03; MacAdams, Marion; 1 sound recordings (1 CD; Duration: 0:16:47) (Box 131, Case 1)